nearlygood.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | NearlyGood.com

NearlyGood.com respects the privacy of the visitors to this website and thus, have a firm commitment to privacy which we uphold. On this page you will find our policies towards information gathering and dissemination practices which cover NearlyGood.com. From now on NearlyGood.com may be referred as 'we', 'us' and 'the site'. 

**Information Gathered**

We may gather information such as your IP address at various points around the site. This includes; when you upload a video, leave a comment, rate an item or follow an internal advertising link. We may also gather information to aid us in diagnosing problems with our website or server or to administer the site. 

Your information will never be used to attempt to identify you or your computer and will never be passed on to any 3rd parties. We do not collect any unique information about you (such as your name or email address) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. 

We occasionally collect information about browser types, operating systems, screen resolution, screen colors, and other information which we can use to help design our web sites. These are basic computer statistics which can only be used to make a demographic of the visitors to the site. 

We gather various user information to provide you with a customized experience on our site. This information helps us tailor website content and advertising to your needs. For this reason, we may ask you to register or to provide personal information in order for you to upload a video, make a comment, rate a video or subscribe to our newsletter. If you choose not to register you may not have access to areas that require personal identification. 

**Cookies**

Our user system makes use of cookies to recognise users which are logged into the site. This allows registered users access to areas of the site that require personal identification such as uploading a video, making comments and rating content. 

You may reject these cookies or receive a notification of when a cookie is set by using the appropriate setting on your web browser. A cookie is a small line of text that is stored within your web browser which allows us to keep a record of logged in users. If you choose to reject cookies from within your browser you may not have access to areas that require personal identification. 

We use various companies to serve advertisements on some of the sites pages. These companies and advertisers may place and access their cookies on your computer. These companies use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. We cannot be held responsible for the content or the privacy policies of these sites. 

**Email Correspondence**

If you provide us with your email address, either by registering a user account or signing up for our newsletter and do not opt-out of receiving email from us, we may from time to time send you emails you with information, including information about selected third parties. If you do not want to receive information from us, you may opt-out either when you initially provide personal information to us in our account registration or when you update your profile. You may also choose to opt-out from certain types of email by following the unsubscribe link which appear on each newsletter. 

**Other**

Our site contains external links, including text links, banners and other ads, to websites we have no control or influence over. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites. You should look at the privacy policy on any external websites if you are unsure. 

Your personal information (account) is password protected, and you should take appropriate measures to protect the secrecy of your password. If you use a computer in a public place or share a computer with others, remember to sign out and close your browser window when you finish a session with us in order to prevent others from accessing your personal information. 

You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of your profile by notifying us if or when any information such as your email address changes. 

Your use of our site, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. By using our Site, you are accepting the practices set out in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. 

This Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. If any changes are made we will attempt to notify users of thoses changes by email or a notice on the website. This may not always be possible, so users are encouraged to check this page. 

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, you can contact us here. 

**Date: July 12th, 2011**
